New England Medical Center Records MS099
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs and audiovisual material, 1880 -- 2009; MS099.001; 86.8 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 159 Digital Object(s)
  - Videotapes, 1979 -- 2009; MS099.001.007
    - University-Community Partnerships: The Mystic Watershed Collaborative, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.239.00010 (Box 239)
    - The Gordon Institute at Tufts University- Emerging Technologies Series. Mobile Communications Networks and New Business Models. tape 1 of 2, 2001-04-20; MS099.001.007.239.00011 (Box 239)
    - Grafton campus, Letter Box Transfer, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.239.00012 (Box 239)
    - Medford Campus, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.239.00013 (Box 239)
    - NEMC Exterior and Eye Center B-Roll, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.239.00014 (Box 239)
    - Medical Facilities. Med Records, 1998; MS099.001.007.239.00015 (Box 239)
    - Wolff Photos number 6, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.240.00001 (Box 240)
    - Measuring thickness of the temporary; Patient 2 starts at 3:09:09, 1996-04-02; MS099.001.007.240.00002 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom (part 1-B) The Origins of the Nuclear Arms Race, 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.240.00003 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom (part 2-A) At the Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.240.00004 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom (part 3-B) The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.240.00005 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom (part 1-A) The Origins of the Nuclear Arms Race, 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.240.00006 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom (part 1-B) The Origins of the Nuclear Arms Race, 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.240.00007 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom (part 3-A) The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.240.00008 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom (part 2-B) At a Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.240.00009 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom number 9: Global Warming, 1991-04-26; MS099.001.007.240.00010 (Box 240)
    - The Global Classroom number 7: The Environment and the Superpowers; Global Atmosphere Pollution, 1989-04-22; MS099.001.007.240.00011 (Box 240)
    - Tufts University, USSR Feed direct record from satellite WIV, 6D (1 of 2), 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.240.00012 (Box 240)
    - Wolff voice over M Schaffer, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.241.00001 (Box 241)
    - Wolff voice over, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.241.00002 (Box 241)
    - Human Nutrition Research Center on aging. Video news release, 1993-10-12-1993-10-13; MS099.001.007.241.00003 (Box 241)
    - President Giscard at Tufts Chen Auditorium, 1996-02-08; MS099.001.007.241.00004 (Box 241)
    - The Global Classroom (part 3-B) The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.241.00005 (Box 241)
    - The Global Classroom (part 3-A) The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.241.00006 (Box 241)
    - Global Classroom Project number 10. Democracy and A Free Press: Soviet feed, 1991-11-02; MS099.001.007.241.00007 (Box 241)
    - Mandir, Masjid Mandal and Marx Democracy in India, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.241.00008 (Box 241)
    - The Global Classroom number 4 - The Comprehensive Test Ban Treaty Debate, 1988-10-22; MS099.001.007.241.00009 (Box 241)
    - New England Eye Center Dedication at the Wang Center (tape 1 of 4), 1993-09-10; MS099.001.007.241.00010 (Box 241)
    - Three Tufts Tests... Students, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.241.00011 (Box 241)
    - NEMC opening 200th Deeb Salem CEO O'Donnell, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.241.00012 (Box 241)
    - 200th anniversary archival photos tape 2, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.241.00013 (Box 241)
    - Tufts Emerson press conference 1, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.241.00014 (Box 241)
    - Boston to Beijing teleconference five minute edit: Tufts University and Sackler Center overview, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.241.00015 (Box 241)
    - Dedication of Floating Hospital, 1982-10-19; MS099.001.007.241.00016 (Box 241)
    - Global Classroom Project number 10 Democracy and a Free Press (tape 1 of 2), 1991-11-02; MS099.001.007.242.00001 (Box 242)
    - Arthur M. Sackler Center; Artist Rendition of Arthur M. Sackler Center, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.242.00002 (Box 242)
    - James Baker/Fares Lecture, 1996; MS099.001.007.242.00003 (Box 242)
    - Global Classroom Project number 10 Democracy & A Free Press (2 of 2), 1991-11-02; MS099.001.007.242.00004 (Box 242)
    - New England Eye Center dedication at the Wang Center (tape 2 of 4), 1993-09-10; MS099.001.007.242.00005 (Box 242)
    - Dedication of Floating Hospital, tape number 1, 1982-10-22; MS099.001.007.242.00006 (Box 242)
    - Documentation of Boston Floating Hospital, tape number 5, 1982-06-01; MS099.001.007.242.00007 (Box 242)
    - Dedication of the Goldie and Louis Trilling House. Dedication of the Edith Rieva and Hyman S. Trilling Chair in Geriatrics. Remarks to the 1990 Graduating Class Tufts University School of Medicine, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.242.00008 (Box 242)
    - New England Eye Center dedication at the Wang Center (tape 4 of4), 1993-09-10; MS099.001.007.242.00009 (Box 242)
    - 2 Wolff photos sub, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.242.00010 (Box 242)
    - The Global Classroom number 7: The Environment and the Superpowers; Global Atmosphere Pollution, 1989-04-22; MS099.001.007.242.00011 (Box 242)
    - The Global Classroom number 9: Global Warming (tape 2 of 2), 1991-04-26; MS099.001.007.242.00012 (Box 242)
    - The Global Classroom The Environment and our Future, 1990-04-21; MS099.001.007.242.00013 (Box 242)
    - Tufts University USSR feed: Direct Record from Satellite wiv, 10D. (tape 2 of 2), 1988-04-09; MS099.001.007.243.00001 (Box 243)
    - Tufts University/Moscow University Global Classroom Project number 6. (tape 2 of 2), 1989-03-04; MS099.001.007.243.00002 (Box 243)
    - Tufts University videoconference: Moscow audio (Russian), translation. (tape 1 of 2), 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.243.00003 (Box 243)
    - The Global Classroom (part 1-B) The Origins of the Nuclear Arms Race, 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.243.00004 (Box 243)
    - Tufts University/Moscow University Global Classroom Project number 6: Composite (tape 2 of 2), 1989-03-06; MS099.001.007.243.00005 (Box 243)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine: The Next Four Years, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.243.00006 (Box 243)
    - Tufts University videoconference: Moscow audio (Russian), Translation, 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.243.00007 (Box 243)
    - Tufts/Moscow State University, 1989-03-06; MS099.001.007.243.00008 (Box 243)
    - Tufts University/Moscow University Global Classroom Project number 6: USSR clean feed, interpreter, 1989-03-04; MS099.001.007.243.00009 (Box 243)
    - The Global Classroom number 7 The Environment and the Superpowers Global Atmosphere Pollution (part 2), 1989-04-22; MS099.001.007.243.00010 (Box 243)
    - Russia's Economic Recovery, 1992-04-04; MS099.001.007.243.00011 (Box 243)
    - James Baker at Tufts Fares 1996, center camera tape 1, MS099.001.007.243.00012 (Box 243)
    - The Global Classroom number 5 The Nuclear Age: Culture and the Bomb, 1988-12-06; MS099.001.007.243.00013 (Box 243)
    - Tufts University/Moscow University The Global Classroom Project number 5, tape 2 of 2, 1988-12-10; MS099.001.007. 244.00001 (Box 244)
    - Tufts University/Moscow University: The Global Classroom Project number 6, tape 2 of 2, 1989-03-04; MS099.001.007. 244.00002 (Box 244)
    - Tufts University USA/USSR Feed tape 2 of 2, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007. 244.00003 (Box 244)
    - Tufts University/Moscow University Global Classroom Project number 4. Reel 2 of 2, 1988-10-22; MS099.001.007. 244.00004 (Box 244)
    - The Global Classroom Project number 10 Democracy and a Free Press, 1991-11-07; MS099.001.007. 244.00005 (Box 244)
    - The Global Classroom Project number 7. tape 1 of 2, 1989-04-22; MS099.001.007. 244.00006 (Box 244)
    - Tufts University/Moscow University Global Classroom Project number 6. tape 1 of 2, 1989-03-04; MS099.001.007. 244.00007 (Box 244)
    - Tufts University USA/USSR composite feed. Reel 2 of 2, 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.245.00001 (Box 245)
    - The Global Classroom Russia's Economic Recovery, 1992-04-04; MS099.001.007.245.00002 (Box 245)
    - The Global Classroom, Soviet clean feed 1 of 2, 1991-04-23; MS099.001.007.245.00003 (Box 245)
    - The Global Classroom Environment and our Future tape 1 of 2, 1990-04-21; MS099.001.007.245.00004 (Box 245)
    - The Global Classroom part 5. tape 1, 1988-12-10; MS099.001.007.245.00005 (Box 245)
    - Tufts Managed Care interview tape 2, 1996-06-19; MS099.001.007.245.00006 (Box 245)
    - Tufts Managed Care interview tape 3, 1996-06-19; MS099.001.007.245.00007 (Box 245)
    - Tisch/Tufts Hollywood (4), 1996-10-10; MS099.001.007.245.00008 (Box 245)
    - Tufts Managed Care interview tape 1, 1996-06-19; MS099.001.007.245.00009 (Box 245)
    - NEMC Cover Shots, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.245.00010 (Box 245)
    - 200th Anniversary archival photos tape 4, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.245.00011 (Box 245)
    - Dedication of Floating Hospital, 1982-10-19; MS099.001.007.246.00001 (Box 246)
    - Dedication of Floating Hospital tape number 2, 1982-10-22; MS099.001.007.246.00002 (Box 246)
    - 200th Anniversary archival photos tape 5, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.246.00003 (Box 246)
    - Dedication of Floating Hospital (tp B), 1982-10-19; MS099.001.007.246.00004 (Box 246)
    - NEMC B-roll, 1995-06; MS099.001.007.246.00005 (Box 246)
    - USA/USSR crew goodbye, 1989-04-22; MS099.001.007.246.00006 (Box 246)
    - Cuban Crisis, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.246.00007 (Box 246)
    - The Global Classroom Project: Democracy and a Free Press, 1991-11-02; MS099.001.007.246.00008 (Box 246)
    - USA Clean Tufts/Moscow Audio ch2, Reel number 2, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.246.00009 (Box 246)
    - Tufts University Students go to Moscow (tape 2 of 2), circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.246.00010 (Box 246)
    - WGBX Broadcast (lots of noise), circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.246.00011 (Box 246)
    - Boston to Beijing teleconference (tape 2 of 2), circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.246.00012 (Box 246)
    - Global Classroom Project number 10 Democracy and a Free Press, 1991-11-02; MS099.001.007.246.00013 (Box 246)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom (part 1-B); The Origins of the Nuclear Arms Race, 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.247.00001 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University- Moscow University. The Global Classroom (part 3-B); The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.247.00002 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University- Moscow University. The Global Classroom (part 2-B): At the Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.247.00003 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University- Moscow University. The Global Classroom (part 2-A): At the Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.247.00004 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University- Moscow University. The Global Classroom (part 2-B): At the Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.247.00005 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University- Moscow University. The Global Classroom (part 2-A): At the Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.247.00006 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University- Moscow University. The Global Classroom (part 2-A): At the Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.247.00007 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University- Moscow University. The Global Classroom (part 3-A): The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.247.00008 (Box 247)
    - Memorial Service Merrill Goldstein, MD, 2000-09-21; MS099.001.007.247.00009 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine; The Next Four Years, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.247.00010 (Box 247)
    - Faces of Floating. Slide show transfer w/music, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.247.00011 (Box 247)
    - Tufts University- Moscow University. The Global Classroom Project number 7 (1 of 2), 1989-04-22; MS099.001.007.247.00012 (Box 247)
    - INT. Fares Tower w/students; Gantcher plaque, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.247.00013 (Box 247)
    - Tisch 1 Tufts 2 Hollywood Panel, 1996-10-10; MS099.001.007.247.00014 (Box 247)
    - Endowed Professorship For Dental Research, 2000-11-09; MS099.001.007.247.00015 (Box 247)
    - 200th Anniversary Celebration. AM- O'Donnell's open; PM- Dorkin Pt. 2, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.247.00016 (Box 247)
    - Educational Media Center, Demo Reel for HNRC, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.248.00001 (Box 248)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom (part 1-B); The Origins of the Nuclear Arms Race, 1988-03-05; MS099.001.007.248.00002 (Box 248)
    - Ed Hill- Gait Banks, M.D., circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.248.00003 (Box 248)
    - Tufts University USA/USSR Composite Feed (2 of 2), circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.248.00004 (Box 248)
    - Tufts University Global Classroom; The Environment and our Future (tape 2 of 2), 1990-04-21; MS099.001.007.248.00005 (Box 248)
    - Russia's Economic Recovery (tape 2), 1992-04-04; MS099.001.007.248.00006 (Box 248)
    - Russia's Economic Recovery (tape 1 of 2), 1992-04-04; MS099.001.007.248.00007 (Box 248)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom (part 3-A); The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.248.00008 (Box 248)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom Project number 4, Studio A Clean Feed (1 of 2), 1988-10-22; MS099.001.007.248.00009 (Box 248)
    - Reel number 3 USA Clean Tufts/ Moscow Audio Ch 2, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.248.00010 (Box 248)
    - USSR Feed Direct Record from Satellite Wiv, 10D (1 of 2), 1988-04-09; MS099.001.007.248.00011 (Box 248)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom number 4; The Comprehensive Test Ban Treaty Debate, 1988-10-22; MS099.001.007.248.00012 (Box 248)
    - 200th Anniversary Seminar PM Session, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.248.00013 (Box 248)
    - Ed Hil-Gait Banks, M.D., circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.248.00014 (Box 248)
    - Russia's Economic Recovery (tape 1 of 2), circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00001 (Box 249)
    - Number 2 Cinque, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00002 (Box 249)
    - London 1. N.H. 2., 1979; MS099.001.007.249.00003 (Box 249)
    - Russia's Economic Recovery Number 2, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00004 (Box 249)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom (part 2-A): At the Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.249.00005 (Box 249)
    - Space Bridge to Moscow, 1988-04-09; MS099.001.007.249.00006 (Box 249)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom (part 3-B): The Cuban Missile Crisis, 1988-04-30; MS099.001.007.249.00007 (Box 249)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom (part 2-B): At the Crossroads: Nuclear Weapons Strategies, 1988; MS099.001.007.249.00008 (Box 249)
    - We Are New England Medical Center, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00009 (Box 249)
    - The Philosophical Bases of Biological Thought. Scott Gilbert, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00010 (Box 249)
    - The Philosophical Bases of Biological Thought. Jean-Jacques Kupiec, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00011 (Box 249)
    - Allen Steere, Grand Rounds, Lyme Disease, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00012 (Box 249)
    - New England Medical Center: Medical Center to the World, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00013 (Box 249)
    - Pneumonia in the Pediatric Patient, 1999-03-05; MS099.001.007.249.00014 (Box 249)
    - Boston/Beijing Teleconference Sackler Building opening, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00015 (Box 249)
    - NEMC logo with Media Selections title, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00016 (Box 249)
    - The Philosophical Bases of Biological Thought. Ana M. Soto, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00017 (Box 249)
    - The Philosophical Bases of Biological Thought. Sahotra Sarkar, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.249.00018 (Box 249)
    - Dr. Steele, tape 2, 1988-12-15; MS099.001.007.249.00019 (Box 249)
    - Dental School B-Roll, NEMC marketing tape 10, 1995-12-05; MS099.001.007.250.00001 (Box 250)
    - Daniel C. Dennett Evolution, Culture and Truth, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00002 (Box 250)
    - Daniel C. Dennett Evolution, Culture and Truth, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00003 (Box 250)
    - Tufts University - Moscow State University. The Global Classroom number 5, The Nuclear Age: Culture and the Bomb, 1988-12-10; MS099.001.007.250.00004 (Box 250)
    - Tisch Library Sports Panel 3, 1996-10-09; MS099.001.007.250.00005 (Box 250)
    - Fares Lecture, James Baker, 1996; MS099.001.007.250.00006 (Box 250)
    - Dedication of Floating Hospital, 1982-10-18; MS099.001.007.250.00007 (Box 250)
    - Tisch Library Honorary Degree 2, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00008 (Box 250)
    - Tufts: A University Poised, Trustee Presentation, 2003-02-07; MS099.001.007.250.00009 (Box 250)
    - Ethnic Diversity at Tufts B-Roll, 1995-03-15; MS099.001.007.250.00010 (Box 250)
    - New England Medical Center, World Class Care, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00011 (Box 250)
    - Daniel C. Dennett Evolution, Culture, and Truth, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00012 (Box 250)
    - Dr. Thomas Posever, interviews with Isaac and Charles, 2005-08-16; MS099.001.007.250.00013 (Box 250)
    - 200th Anniversary Archives tape 7, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00014 (Box 250)
    - Wolff photos number 3, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00015 (Box 250)
    - Wolff photos tape 4, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00016 (Box 250)
    - The Philosophical Bases of Biological Thought, Carlos Sonnenschein, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.250.00017 (Box 250)
    - NEMC marketing video, ICU, Building/Atrium, 1995-10-16; MS099.001.007.250.00018 (Box 250)
    - NEMC marketing video, Dr. Furie Wesruew, 4, 1995-10-16; MS099.001.007.250.00019 (Box 250)
    - New England Medical Center marketing video 6, 1995-11-09; MS099.001.007.250.00020 (Box 250)
    - Tufts full mix program, reel 1, 1990-04-21; MS099.001.007.250.00021 (Box 250)
    - Tufts School of Medicine, Centennial Celebration, tape 4, 1993-04-15; MS099.001.007.251.00001 (Box 251)
    - Memorial Service for Sheldon M. Wolff, M.D. (tape 1 of 2), circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.251.00002 (Box 251)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom part 5, tape 2, 1988-12-10; MS099.001.007.251.00003 (Box 251)
    - 200th Anniversary Celebration 4 PM, 1996-09-27; MS099.001.007.251.00004 (Box 251)
    - The Global Classroom The Environment and Our Future (1 of 2), 1990-04-21; MS099.001.007.251.00005 (Box 251)
    - Tufts University- Moscow State University. The Global Classroom Project number 5 (1 of 2), 1988-12-10; MS099.001.007.251.00006 (Box 251)
    - New England Medical Center; Medical Center to the World, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.251.00007 (Box 251)
    - Tail End Moscow Telecom, tape number 3, 1986-03-20; MS099.001.007.251.00008 (Box 251)
    - Arthur Sackler Festschrift, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.251.00009 (Box 251)
    - President Giscard at Tufts Cohen Auditorium number 1, 1996-02-08; MS099.001.007.251.00010 (Box 251)
    - Floating Hospital Dedication, tape number 5, 1982-10-18; MS099.001.007.251.00011 (Box 251)
    - Dedication Floating Hospital, tape number 3, 1982-10-22; MS099.001.007.251.00012 (Box 251)
    - Tisch/Tufts Hollywood 3, 1996-10-10; MS099.001.007.251.00013 (Box 251)
    - Fares Press Platform number 2, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.251.00014 (Box 251)
    - Millstein Boylan tape 2, 1996-05-23; MS099.001.007.252.00001 (Box 252)
    - Wolff MX number 2, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.252.00002 (Box 252)
    - O'Donnell Patient: Corso, tape 8, Audio ch 2, 1996-03-07; MS099.001.007.252.00003 (Box 252)
    - Fares Lecture James Baker, 1996-11-05; MS099.001.007.252.00004 (Box 252)
    - O'Donnell Patient: Corso tape 6, 1996-03-07; MS099.001.007.252.00005 (Box 252)
    - O'Donnell Patient: Corso tape 7 audio ch 2, 1996-03-07; MS099.001.007.252.00006 (Box 252)
    - Tufts Development Meeting, 1996-03-22; MS099.001.007.252.00007 (Box 252)
    - Hong Kong Award Ceremony at Goddard Chapel (Medford Campus), 1995-09-07; MS099.001.007.252.00008 (Box 252)
    - Dr. Berk Laboratory dedication number 4, 1988-04-28; MS099.001.007.252.00009 (Box 252)
    - Tisch Library B. Roll plaques, etc., circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.252.00010 (Box 252)
    - Dr. Berk Laboratory dedication, 1988-04-28; MS099.001.007.252.00011 (Box 252)
    - O'Donnell Patient: Corso tape 9, 1996-03-07; MS099.001.007.252.00012 (Box 252)
    - Dean Barbara Chase, Family Day Speech, 1995-10-02; MS099.001.007.252.00013 (Box 252)
    - Dr. Berk Laboratory dedication number 3, 1988-04-28; MS099.001.007.252.00014 (Box 252)
    - Honorary Degree 3 Ribbon Cutting Library int. + ext., circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.252.00015 (Box 252)
    - Wolff Photos number 1, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.252.00016 (Box 252)
    - O'Donnell, tape 1, 1994-03-10; MS099.001.007.252.00017 (Box 252)
    - Sheldon M. Wolff, MD: Man of Achievement, Integrity and Courage, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.253.00001 (Box 253)
    - Honorary Degrees, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.253.00002 (Box 253)
    - Tisch Library Dedication, tape 1, Forrest Gump at the Millennium, 1996-10-10; MS099.001.007.253.00003 (Box 253)
    - Two days in October, The Tisch Library, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.253.00004 (Box 253)
    - Mr. Chairman Tribute to Nelson Gifford, 1995-11; MS099.001.007.253.00005 (Box 253)
    - Tufts School of Medicine Centennial Celebration, 1993-04-15; MS099.001.007.253.00006 (Box 253)
    - Hong Kong Ceremony at Goddard Chapel, Medford, 1995-09-07; MS099.001.007.253.00007 (Box 253)
    - Highlights from the First International Conference on Landmine Survivors, 1998; MS099.001.007.253.00008 (Box 253)
    - The Global Classroom Project number 10 Democracy and a Free Press, 1991-11-02; MS099.001.007.253.00009 (Box 253)
    - O'Donnell, tape 2 cont. and tape 3, 1994-03-10; MS099.001.007.253.00010 (Box 253)
    - O'Donnell, tape 4 cont., 1994-03-10; MS099.001.007.253.00011 (Box 253)
    - GCP number 9 Global Warming RUSSIAN, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.253.00012 (Box 253)
    - O'Donnell, tape 3 cont. and tape 4, 1994-03-10; MS099.001.007.253.00013 (Box 253)
    - O'Donnell OR footage, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.254.00001 (Box 254)
    - Wolff Photo Sub, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.254.00002 (Box 254)
    - A Tribute to Sheldon M. Wolff, M.D., 1995-07-31; MS099.001.007.254.00003 (Box 254)
    - Dr. O'Donnell, Resection of a suprarenal intracaval tumor audio ch 2, 1998; MS099.001.007.254.00004 (Box 254)
    - A Dinner to honor Jerome P. Kassirer, M.D., 1991-06-27; MS099.001.007.254.00005 (Box 254)
    - Governmental Leadership: Investing in Children, Edward Kennedy, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.254.00006 (Box 254)
    - Voluntary Action, Marian Heard, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.254.00007 (Box 254)
    - Social Entrepreneurship, Vanessa Kirsch, President, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.254.00008 (Box 254)
    - The Civil Rights Movement entering the 21st century, Antonia Hernandez, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.254.00009 (Box 254)
    - Electoral Leadership: Revitalizing a City, Michael Capuano, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.254.00010 (Box 254)
    - Mass Media and Public Service, Arthur Ochs Sulzberger, Jr., circa 1980 -- 2009; MS099.001.007.254.00011 (Box 254)